{
  "id": "resolutions",
  "name": "Resolutions",
  "title": "This cheat sheet lists screen sizes, viewport size and CSS media queries for popular Phones, Tablets, Laptops and Watches",
  "icon": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Fechin/reference/main/source/assets/icon/resolutions.svg",
  "sections": [
    {
      "id": "intro",
      "title": "Intro",
      "startIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "id": "s1",
      "title": "Getting Started",
      "startIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "s2",
      "title": "Lists of Resolutions",
      "startIndex": 3
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": "intro-0",
      "sectionId": "intro",
      "title": "Intro",
      "kind": "text",
      "body": "This cheat sheet lists screen sizes, viewport size and CSS media queries for popular Phones, Tablets, Laptops and Watches"
    },
    {
      "id": "s1-1",
      "sectionId": "s1",
      "title": "Introduction",
      "kind": "text",
      "body": "• Resolution is the number of pixels (individual points of color)\n• Viewport is defined by the size of the rectangle filled by a web page on your screen\n• Screen resolution refers to the clarity of the text and images displayed on your screen\n• For design"
    },
    {
      "id": "s1-2",
      "sectionId": "s1",
      "title": "Multi-format of Resolutions",
      "kind": "text",
      "body": "• [Markdown Table](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-markdown?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [Template](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-template?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [LaTeX Table](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-latex?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [CSV](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-csv?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [Excel](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-excel?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [JSON Array](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-json?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [HTML Table](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-html?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [Insert SQL](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-sql?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [YAML Sequence](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-yaml?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [XML](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-xml?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [ASCII](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-ascii?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [MediaWiki Table](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-mediawiki?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [AsciiDoc Table](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-asciidoc?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [Jira Table](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-jira?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [Textile Table](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-textile?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [reStructuredText](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-restructuredtext?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [PHP Array](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-php?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [Ruby Array](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-ruby?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [ASP Array](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-asp?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [ActionScript](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-actionscript?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [BBCode](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-bbcode?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [PDF](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-pdf?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)\n• [JPEG](https://tableconvert.com/html-to-jpeg?data=https://cheatsheets.zip/resolutions#TableGenerator)"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-3",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone 11 (2019)",
      "back": "6.1 <sub>inch</sub> | 828 x 1792 <sub>px</sub> | 414 x 896 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iOS 13.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-4",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone 11 Pro (2019)",
      "back": "5.8 <sub>inch</sub> | 1125 x 2436 <sub>px</sub> | 375 x 812 <sub>px</sub> | 458 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | iOS 13.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-5",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone 11 Pro Max (2019)",
      "back": "6.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 1242 x 2688 <sub>px</sub> | 414 x 896 <sub>px</sub> | 458 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | iOS 13.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-6",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone 12 (2020)",
      "back": "6.1 <sub>inch</sub> | 1170 x 2532 <sub>px</sub> | 390 x 844 <sub>px</sub> | 460 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | iOS 14.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-7",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone 12 Pro (2020)",
      "back": "6.1 <sub>inch</sub> | 1170 x 2532 <sub>px</sub> | 390 x 844 <sub>px</sub> | 460 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | iOS 14.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-8",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone 12 Pro Max (2020)",
      "back": "6.7 <sub>inch</sub> | 1284 x 2778 <sub>px</sub> | 428 x 926 <sub>px</sub> | 458 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | iOS 14.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-9",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone 12 mini (2020)",
      "back": "5.4 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2340 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 780 <sub>px</sub> | 476 <sub>ppi</sub> | 159 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | iOS 14.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-10",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone 5",
      "back": "4 <sub>inch</sub> | 640 x 1136 <sub>px</sub> | 320 x 568 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iOS 6"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-11",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone 5c",
      "back": "4 <sub>inch</sub> | 640 x 1136 <sub>px</sub> | 320 x 568 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iOS 7"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-12",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone 5s",
      "back": "4 <sub>inch</sub> | 640 x 1136 <sub>px</sub> | 320 x 568 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iOS 7"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-13",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone 6",
      "back": "4.7 <sub>inch</sub> | 750 x 1334 <sub>px</sub> | 375 x 667 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iOS 8"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-14",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone 6s",
      "back": "4.7 <sub>inch</sub> | 750 x 1334 <sub>px</sub> | 375 x 667 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iOS 9"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-15",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone 6s Plus",
      "back": "5.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 1920 <sub>px</sub> | 414 x 736 <sub>px</sub> | 401 <sub>ppi</sub> | 134 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.0 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | iOS 9"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-16",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone 7",
      "back": "4.7 <sub>inch</sub> | 750 x 1334 <sub>px</sub> | 375 x 667 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iOS 10.0.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-17",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone 7 Plus",
      "back": "5.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 1920 <sub>px</sub> | 414 x 736 <sub>px</sub> | 401 <sub>ppi</sub> | 134 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.0 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | iOS 10.0.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-18",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone 8",
      "back": "4.7 <sub>inch</sub> | 750 x 1334 <sub>px</sub> | 375 x 667 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iOS 11"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-19",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone 8 Plus",
      "back": "5.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 1920 <sub>px</sub> | 414 x 736 <sub>px</sub> | 401 <sub>ppi</sub> | 134 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.0 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | iOS 11"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-20",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone SE",
      "back": "4.0 <sub>inch</sub> | 640 x 1136 <sub>px</sub> | 320 x 568 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iOS 9.3.2"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-21",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone SE (2020)",
      "back": "4.7 <sub>inch</sub> | 750 x 1334 <sub>px</sub> | 375 x 667 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iOS 13.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-22",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone X",
      "back": "5.8 <sub>inch</sub> | 1125 x 2436 <sub>px</sub> | 375 x 812 <sub>px</sub> | 458 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.0 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | iOS 11.1.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-23",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone XR",
      "back": "6.1 <sub>inch</sub> | 828 x 1792 <sub>px</sub> | 414 x 896 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iOS 12"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-24",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone XS",
      "back": "5.8 <sub>inch</sub> | 1125 x 2436 <sub>px</sub> | 375 x 812 <sub>px</sub> | 458 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.0 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | iOS 12"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-25",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPhone XS Max",
      "back": "6.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 1242 x 2688 <sub>px</sub> | 414 x 896 <sub>px</sub> | 458 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.0 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | iOS 12"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-26",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Google Pixel",
      "back": "5.0 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 1920 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 732 <sub>px</sub> | 441 <sub>ppi</sub> | 168 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 7.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-27",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Google Pixel",
      "back": "5.0 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 1920 <sub>px</sub> | 411 x 731 <sub>px</sub> | 441 <sub>ppi</sub> | 168 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.6 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 7.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-28",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Google Pixel 2",
      "back": "5.0 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 1920 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 732 <sub>px</sub> | 441 <sub>ppi</sub> | 168 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 8.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-29",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Google Pixel 2 XL",
      "back": "6.0 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 2880 <sub>px</sub> |  | 538 <sub>ppi</sub> | 154 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.5 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 8.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-30",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Google Pixel 3 (2018)",
      "back": "5.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2160 <sub>px</sub> | 393 x 786 <sub>px</sub> | 443 <sub>ppi</sub> | 161 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.75 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-31",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Google Pixel 3 XL (2018)",
      "back": "6.3 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 2960 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 846 <sub>px</sub> | 523 <sub>ppi</sub> | 149 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.5 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-32",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Google Pixel 3a (2019)",
      "back": "5.6 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2220 <sub>px</sub> | 393 x 808 <sub>px</sub> | 441 <sub>ppi</sub> | 160 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.75 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-33",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Google Pixel 3a XL (2019)",
      "back": "6 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2160 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 823 <sub>px</sub> | 402 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-34",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Google Pixel 4 (2019)",
      "back": "5.7 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2280 <sub>px</sub> | 393 x 830 <sub>px</sub> | 444 <sub>ppi</sub> | 161 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.75 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-35",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Google Pixel 4 XL (2019)",
      "back": "6.3 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 3040 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 869 <sub>px</sub> | 537 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.5 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 10"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-36",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Google Pixel 4a (2020)",
      "back": "5.81 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2340 <sub>px</sub> | 393 x 851 <sub>px</sub> | 443 <sub>ppi</sub> | 161 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.75 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-37",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Google Pixel 5 (2020)",
      "back": "6 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2340 <sub>px</sub> | 393 x 851 <sub>px</sub> | 432 <sub>ppi</sub> | 157 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.75 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 11.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-38",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Google Pixel XL",
      "back": "5.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 2560 <sub>px</sub> |  | 534 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.5 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 7.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-39",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "HTC Desire 10 Lifestyle",
      "back": "5.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 720 x 1280 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 640 <sub>px</sub> | 267 <sub>ppi</sub> | 134 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | Android 6.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-40",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "HTC Desire 628",
      "back": "5.0 <sub>inch</sub> | 720 x 1280 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 640 <sub>px</sub> | 294 <sub>ppi</sub> | 147 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | Android 5.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-41",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Honor 6X (2016)",
      "back": "5.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 1920 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 640 <sub>px</sub> | 403 <sub>ppi</sub> | 134 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 6.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-42",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Honor 7X (2017)",
      "back": "5.93 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2160 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 720 <sub>px</sub> | 407 <sub>ppi</sub> | 136 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 7.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-43",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Honor 8X (2018)",
      "back": "6.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2340 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 780 <sub>px</sub> | 397 <sub>ppi</sub> | 132 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 8.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-44",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Honor 9X (2019)",
      "back": "6.59 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2340 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 780 <sub>px</sub> | 391 <sub>ppi</sub> | 130 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-45",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Huawei Mate 10 Lite (2017)",
      "back": "5.9 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2160 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 720 <sub>px</sub> | 409 <sub>ppi</sub> | 136 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 7.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-46",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Huawei Mate 20 Lite (2018)",
      "back": "6.3 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2340 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 780 <sub>px</sub> | 409 <sub>ppi</sub> | 136 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 8.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-47",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Huawei Mate 20 Pro (2018)",
      "back": "6.39 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 3120 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 780 <sub>px</sub> | 538 <sub>ppi</sub> | 135 <sub>ppi</sub> | 4 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-48",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Huawei Mate 30 (2019)",
      "back": "6.62 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2340 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 780 <sub>px</sub> | 389 <sub>ppi</sub> | 130 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-49",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Huawei Mate 30 Pro (2019)",
      "back": "6.53 <sub>inch</sub> | 1176 x 2400 <sub>px</sub> | 392 x 800 <sub>px</sub> | 409 <sub>ppi</sub> | 136 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-50",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Huawei Nova 7i (2020)",
      "back": "6.4 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2310 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 770 <sub>px</sub> | 398 <sub>ppi</sub> | 133 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-51",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Huawei Y9 Prime (2019)",
      "back": "6.59 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2340 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 780 <sub>px</sub> | 391 <sub>ppi</sub> | 130 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-52",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Huawei Y9s (2019)",
      "back": "6.59 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2340 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 780 <sub>px</sub> | 391 <sub>ppi</sub> | 130 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-53",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "LG G5",
      "back": "5.3 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 2560 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 640 <sub>px</sub> | 554 <sub>ppi</sub> | 139 <sub>ppi</sub> | 4.0 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 6.0.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-54",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Motorola Moto E5 Plus",
      "back": "6.0 <sub>inch</sub> | 720 x 1440 <sub>px</sub> |  | 268 <sub>ppi</sub> | 134 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | Android 8.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-55",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "OnePlus 6",
      "back": "6.28 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2280 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 869 <sub>px</sub> | 402 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 8.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-56",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "OnePlus 6T",
      "back": "6.41 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2340 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 892 <sub>px</sub> | 402 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-57",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "OnePlus 7",
      "back": "6.41 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2340 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 892 <sub>px</sub> | 402 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-58",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "OnePlus 7 Pro",
      "back": "6.67 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 3120 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 892 <sub>px</sub> | 516 <sub>ppi</sub> | 147 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.5 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-59",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "OnePlus 7T (2019)",
      "back": "6.55 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2400 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 914 <sub>px</sub> | 402 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-60",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "OnePlus 8 (2020)",
      "back": "6.55 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2400 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 915 <sub>px</sub> | 402 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-61",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "OnePlus 8 Pro (2020)",
      "back": "6.78 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 3168 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 906 <sub>px</sub> | 513 <sub>ppi</sub> | 147 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.5 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-62",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "OnePlus 8T (2020)",
      "back": "6.55 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2400 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 914 <sub>px</sub> | 402 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 11.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-63",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "OnePlus Nord (2020)",
      "back": "6.44 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2400 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 915 <sub>px</sub> | 408 <sub>ppi</sub> | 155 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-64",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Redmi Note 9 Pro (2020)",
      "back": "6.67 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2400 <sub>px</sub> | 393 x 873 <sub>px</sub> | 395 <sub>ppi</sub> | 144 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.75 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-65",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung A50 (2019)",
      "back": "6.4 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2340 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 892 <sub>px</sub> | 403 <sub>ppi</sub> | 154 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-66",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy A30 (2019)",
      "back": "6.4 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2340 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 892 <sub>px</sub> | 403 <sub>ppi</sub> | 154 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-67",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy A50s (2019)",
      "back": "6.4 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2340 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 892 <sub>px</sub> | 403 <sub>ppi</sub> | 154 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-68",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy A51 (2019)",
      "back": "6.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2400 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 914 <sub>px</sub> | 405 <sub>ppi</sub> | 154 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-69",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy A6s",
      "back": "6.0 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2160 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 720 <sub>px</sub> | 402 <sub>ppi</sub> | 134 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.0 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 8.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-70",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy A70s (2019)",
      "back": "6.7 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2400 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 914 <sub>px</sub> | 393 <sub>ppi</sub> | 150 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-71",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy A71 (2020)",
      "back": "6.7 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2400 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 914 <sub>px</sub> | 393 <sub>ppi</sub> | 150 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-72",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy Fold (2019)",
      "back": "7.3 <sub>inch</sub> | 1536 x 2152 <sub>px</sub> | 768 x 1076 <sub>px</sub> | 362 <sub>ppi</sub> | 181 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-73",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy J4",
      "back": "5.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 720 x 1280 <sub>px</sub> |  |  | 134 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | Android 8.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-74",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy J5",
      "back": "5.0 <sub>inch</sub> | 720 x 1280 <sub>px</sub> |  | 294 <sub>ppi</sub> |  | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | Android 5.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-75",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy J5 Prime",
      "back": "5.0 <sub>inch</sub> | 720 x 1280 <sub>px</sub> |  | 294 <sub>ppi</sub> | 147 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | Android 6.0.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-76",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy J6",
      "back": "5.6 <sub>inch</sub> | 720 x 1480 <sub>px</sub> |  | 293 <sub>ppi</sub> | 147 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | Android 8.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-77",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy J7",
      "back": "5.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 720 x 1280 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 640 <sub>px</sub> | 267 <sub>ppi</sub> | 134 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | Android 6.0.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-78",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy J7 Prime",
      "back": "5.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 1920 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 640 <sub>px</sub> | 401 <sub>ppi</sub> | 134 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.0 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 6.0.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-79",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy J7 Prime2 (2018)",
      "back": "5.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 1920 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 732 <sub>px</sub> | 401 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 7.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-80",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy J7 Pro",
      "back": "5.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 1920 <sub>px</sub> |  | 401 <sub>ppi</sub> | 134 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 7.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-81",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy J8",
      "back": "6.0 <sub>inch</sub> | 720 x 1480 <sub>px</sub> |  | 274 <sub>ppi</sub> | 137 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | Android 8.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-82",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy Note20 (2020)",
      "back": "6.7 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2400 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 915 <sub>px</sub> | 393 <sub>ppi</sub> | 150 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-83",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy Note20 Ultra (2020)",
      "back": "6.9 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 3088 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 883 <sub>px</sub> | 496 <sub>ppi</sub> | 142 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.5 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-84",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy Note8",
      "back": "6.3 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 2960 <sub>px</sub> |  | 521 <sub>ppi</sub> | 149 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.5 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 7.1.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-85",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy On8",
      "back": "5.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 1920 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 640 <sub>px</sub> | 401 <sub>ppi</sub> | 134 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.0 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 6.0.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-86",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy S10",
      "back": "6.1 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 3040 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 760 <sub>px</sub> | 550 <sub>ppi</sub> | 138 <sub>ppi</sub> | 4 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-87",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy S10 Lite (2020)",
      "back": "6.7 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2400 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 914 <sub>px</sub> | 394 <sub>ppi</sub> | 150 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-88",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy S10+",
      "back": "6.4 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 3040 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 869 <sub>px</sub> | 522 <sub>ppi</sub> | 149 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.5 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-89",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy S20 (2020)",
      "back": "6.4 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 3200 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 800 <sub>px</sub> | 563 <sub>ppi</sub> | 141 <sub>ppi</sub> | 4 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-90",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy S20 FE (2020)",
      "back": "6.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2400 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 914 <sub>px</sub> | 407 <sub>ppi</sub> | 155 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-91",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy S20 Ultra (2020)",
      "back": "6.9 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 3200 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 915 <sub>px</sub> | 511 <sub>ppi</sub> | 146 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.5 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-92",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy S20+ (2020)",
      "back": "6.7 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 3200 <sub>px</sub> | 384 x 854 <sub>px</sub> | 525 <sub>ppi</sub> | 140 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.75 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-93",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy S21 Ultra (2021)",
      "back": "6.8 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 3200 <sub>px</sub> | 384 x 854 <sub>px</sub> | 515 <sub>ppi</sub> | 137 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.75 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 11.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-94",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy S8",
      "back": "5.8 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 2960 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 740 <sub>px</sub> | 570 <sub>ppi</sub> | 142 <sub>ppi</sub> | 4.0 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 7.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-95",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy S8+",
      "back": "6.2 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 2960 <sub>px</sub> |  | 529 <sub>ppi</sub> | 132 <sub>ppi</sub> | 4.0 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 7.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-96",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy S9",
      "back": "5.8 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 2960 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 740 <sub>px</sub> | 570 <sub>ppi</sub> | 142 <sub>ppi</sub> | 4.0 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 8.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-97",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy S9+",
      "back": "6.2 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 2960 <sub>px</sub> |  | 529 <sub>ppi</sub> | 151 <sub>ppi</sub> | 4 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 8.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-98",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy Z Flip (2020)",
      "back": "6.7 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2636 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 1004 <sub>px</sub> | 425 <sub>ppi</sub> | 162 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-99",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy Z Fold2 (2020)",
      "back": "7.6 <sub>inch</sub> | 1768 x 2208 <sub>px</sub> | 884 x 1104 <sub>px</sub> | 373 <sub>ppi</sub> | 187 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | Android 10.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-100",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Note10 (2019)",
      "back": "6.3 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2280 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 869 <sub>px</sub> | 401 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.625 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-101",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Note10+ (2019)",
      "back": "6.8 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 3040 <sub>px</sub> | 412 x 869 <sub>px</sub> | 498 <sub>ppi</sub> | 142 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.5 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-102",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung S6",
      "back": "5.1 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 2560 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 640 <sub>px</sub> | 577 <sub>ppi</sub> | 144 <sub>ppi</sub> | 4.0 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 5.0.2"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-103",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung S6 edge",
      "back": "5.1 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 2560 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 640 <sub>px</sub> | 577 <sub>ppi</sub> | 144 <sub>ppi</sub> | 4.0 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 5.0.2"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-104",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung S7",
      "back": "5.1 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 2560 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 640 <sub>px</sub> | 577 <sub>ppi</sub> | 144 <sub>ppi</sub> | 4.0 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 6.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-105",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung S7 edge",
      "back": "5.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 2560 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 640 <sub>px</sub> | 534 <sub>ppi</sub> | 153 <sub>ppi</sub> | 4.0 <sub>xxxhdpi</sub> | Android 6.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-106",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Sony Xperia X",
      "back": "5 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 1920 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 640 <sub>px</sub> | 441 <sub>ppi</sub> | 147 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.0 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 6.0.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-107",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Sony Xperia XZ",
      "back": "5.2 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 1920 <sub>px</sub> | 360 x 640 <sub>px</sub> | 424 <sub>ppi</sub> | 141 <sub>ppi</sub> | 3.0 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 6.0.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-108",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Xiaomi Redmi Note 7 (2019)",
      "back": "6.3 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2340 <sub>px</sub> | 393 x 851 <sub>px</sub> | 409 <sub>ppi</sub> | 149 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.75 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-109",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Xiaomi Redmi Note 8 (2019)",
      "back": "6.3 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2340 <sub>px</sub> | 393 x 851 <sub>px</sub> | 409 <sub>ppi</sub> | 149 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.75 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-110",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Mobile Phones",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Xiaomi Redmi Note 8 Pro (2019)",
      "back": "6.53 <sub>inch</sub> | 1080 x 2340 <sub>px</sub> | 393 x 851 <sub>px</sub> | 395 <sub>ppi</sub> | 144 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.75 <sub>xxhdpi</sub> | Android 9.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-111",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Tablets",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPad 10.2\" (2019)",
      "back": "10.2 <sub>inch</sub> | 1620 x 2160 <sub>px</sub> | 810 x 1080 <sub>px</sub> | 264 <sub>ppi</sub> | 132 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iPadOS 13.1.2"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-112",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Tablets",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPad 10.2\" (2020)",
      "back": "10.2 <sub>inch</sub> | 1620 x 2160 <sub>px</sub> | 810 x 1080 <sub>px</sub> | 264 <sub>ppi</sub> | 132 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iPadOS 14"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-113",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Tablets",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPad Air",
      "back": "9.7 <sub>inch</sub> | 1536 x 2048 <sub>px</sub> | 768 x 1024 <sub>px</sub> | 264 <sub>ppi</sub> | 132 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iOS 7"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-114",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Tablets",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPad Air 10.5\" (2019)",
      "back": "10.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 1668 x 2224 <sub>px</sub> | 834 x 1112 <sub>px</sub> | 264 <sub>ppi</sub> | 132 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iPadOS 13.1.2"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-115",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Tablets",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPad Air 10.9\" (2020)",
      "back": "10.9 <sub>inch</sub> | 1640 x 2360 <sub>px</sub> | 820 x 1180 <sub>px</sub> | 264 <sub>ppi</sub> | 132 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iPadOS 14"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-116",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Tablets",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPad Air 2",
      "back": "9.7 <sub>inch</sub> | 1536 x 2048 <sub>px</sub> | 768 x 1024 <sub>px</sub> | 264 <sub>ppi</sub> | 132 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iOS 8.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-117",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Tablets",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPad Mini 7.9\" (2019)",
      "back": "7.9 <sub>inch</sub> | 1536 x 2048 <sub>px</sub> | 768 x 1024 <sub>px</sub> | 324 <sub>ppi</sub> | 162 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iPadOS 13.1.2"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-118",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Tablets",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPad Pro",
      "back": "12.9 <sub>inch</sub> | 2048 x 2732 <sub>px</sub> | 1024 x 1366 <sub>px</sub> | 264 <sub>ppi</sub> | 132 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iOS 9"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-119",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Tablets",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPad Pro 10.5 (2017)",
      "back": "10.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 1668 x 2224 <sub>px</sub> | 834 x 1112 <sub>px</sub> | 264 <sub>ppi</sub> | 132 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iOS 11"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-120",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Tablets",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPad Pro 11\" (2018)",
      "back": "11 <sub>inch</sub> | 1668 x 2388 <sub>px</sub> | 834 x 1194 <sub>px</sub> | 264 <sub>ppi</sub> | 132 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iPadOS 13.1.2"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-121",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Tablets",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPad Pro 11\" (2020)",
      "back": "11 <sub>inch</sub> | 1668 x 2388 <sub>px</sub> | 834 x 1194 <sub>px</sub> | 264 <sub>ppi</sub> | 132 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iPadOS 13.4"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-122",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Tablets",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPad Pro 12.9\" (2018)",
      "back": "12.9 <sub>inch</sub> | 2048 x 2732 <sub>px</sub> | 1024 x 1366 <sub>px</sub> | 264 <sub>ppi</sub> | 132 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iPadOS 13.1.2"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-123",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Tablets",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPad Pro 12.9\" (2020)",
      "back": "12.9 <sub>inch</sub> | 2048 x 2732 <sub>px</sub> | 1024 x 1366 <sub>px</sub> | 264 <sub>ppi</sub> | 132 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iPadOS 13.4"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-124",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Tablets",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPad Pro 9.7",
      "back": "9.7 <sub>inch</sub> | 1536 x 2048 <sub>px</sub> | 768 x 1024 <sub>px</sub> | 264 <sub>ppi</sub> | 132 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iOS 9.3.2"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-125",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Tablets",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPad Pro 9.7 (2017)",
      "back": "9.7 <sub>inch</sub> | 1536 x 2048 <sub>px</sub> | 768 x 1024 <sub>px</sub> | 264 <sub>ppi</sub> | 132 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iOS 10.3"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-126",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Tablets",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPad mini 3",
      "back": "7.9 <sub>inch</sub> | 1536 x 2048 <sub>px</sub> | 768 x 1024 <sub>px</sub> | 324 <sub>ppi</sub> | 132 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iOS 9"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-127",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Tablets",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple iPad mini 4",
      "back": "7.9 <sub>inch</sub> | 1536 x 2048 <sub>px</sub> | 768 x 1024 <sub>px</sub> | 324 <sub>ppi</sub> | 162 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | iOS 8.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-128",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Tablets",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Google Pixel C (2015)",
      "back": "10.2 <sub>inch</sub> | 2560x1800 <sub>px</sub> | 1280 x 900 <sub>px</sub> | 308 <sub>ppi</sub> | 154 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | Android 6.0.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-129",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook 2015 12\"",
      "back": "12 <sub>inch</sub> | 2304 x 1440 <sub>px</sub> | 1280 x 800 <sub>px</sub> | 226 <sub>ppi</sub> | 113 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | macOS Sierra"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-130",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook 2016 12\"",
      "back": "12 <sub>inch</sub> | 2304 x 1440 <sub>px</sub> | 1280 x 800 <sub>px</sub> | 226 <sub>ppi</sub> | 113 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | macOS Sierra"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-131",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook 2017 12\"",
      "back": "12 <sub>inch</sub> | 2304 x 1440 <sub>px</sub> | 1280 x 800 <sub>px</sub> | 226 <sub>ppi</sub> | 113 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | macOS Sierra"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-132",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook Air 2014 11\"",
      "back": "11.6 <sub>inch</sub> | 1366 x 768 <sub>px</sub> | 1366 x 768 <sub>px</sub> | 135 <sub>ppi</sub> | 135 <sub>ppi</sub> | 1.0 <sub>mdpi</sub> | OS X Mavericks"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-133",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook Air 2014 13\"",
      "back": "13.3 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 900 <sub>px</sub> | 1440 x 900 <sub>px</sub> | 128 <sub>ppi</sub> | 128 <sub>ppi</sub> | 1.0 <sub>mdpi</sub> | OS X Mavericks"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-134",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook Air 2015 11\"",
      "back": "11.6 <sub>inch</sub> | 1366 x 768 <sub>px</sub> | 1366 x 768 <sub>px</sub> | 135 <sub>ppi</sub> | 135 <sub>ppi</sub> | 1.0 <sub>mdpi</sub> | OS X El Capitan"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-135",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook Air 2015 13\"",
      "back": "13.3 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 900 <sub>px</sub> | 1440 x 900 <sub>px</sub> | 128 <sub>ppi</sub> | 128 <sub>ppi</sub> | 1.0 <sub>mdpi</sub> | macOS Sierra"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-136",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook Air 2017 13\"",
      "back": "13.3 <sub>inch</sub> | 1440 x 900 <sub>px</sub> | 1440 x 900 <sub>px</sub> | 128 <sub>ppi</sub> | 128 <sub>ppi</sub> | 1.0 <sub>mdpi</sub> | macOS Mojave"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-137",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook Air 2018 13\"",
      "back": "13.3 <sub>inch</sub> | 2560 x 1600 <sub>px</sub> | 1280 x 800 <sub>px</sub> | 227 <sub>ppi</sub> | 113 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | macOS Mojave"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-138",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook Air 2020 13\"",
      "back": "13.3 <sub>inch</sub> | 2560 x 1600 <sub>px</sub> | 1280 x 800 <sub>px</sub> | 227 <sub>ppi</sub> | 114 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | macOS Catalina"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-139",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook Pro 13\" 2018",
      "back": "13.3 <sub>inch</sub> | 2560 x 1600 <sub>px</sub> | 1280 x 800 <sub>px</sub> | 227 <sub>ppi</sub> | 113 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | macOS Mojave"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-140",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook Pro 15\" 2018",
      "back": "15.4 <sub>inch</sub> | 2880 x 1800 <sub>px</sub> | 1440 x 900 <sub>px</sub> | 220 <sub>ppi</sub> | 112 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | macOS Mojave"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-141",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook Pro 16\" 2019",
      "back": "16 <sub>inch</sub> | 3072 x 1920 <sub>px</sub> | 1536 x 960 <sub>px</sub> | 226 <sub>ppi</sub> | 113 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | macOS Catalina"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-142",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook Pro 2014 13\"",
      "back": "13.4 <sub>inch</sub> | 2560 x 1600 <sub>px</sub> | 1280 x 800 <sub>px</sub> | 227 <sub>ppi</sub> | 113 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | macOS Sierra"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-143",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook Pro 2014 15\"",
      "back": "15.4 <sub>inch</sub> | 2880 x 1800 <sub>px</sub> | 1440 x 900 <sub>px</sub> | 220 <sub>ppi</sub> | 112 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | macOS Sierra"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-144",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook Pro 2015 13\"",
      "back": "13.4 <sub>inch</sub> | 2560 x 1600 <sub>px</sub> | 1280 x 800 <sub>px</sub> | 227 <sub>ppi</sub> | 113 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | macOS Sierra"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-145",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook Pro 2015 15\"",
      "back": "15.4 <sub>inch</sub> | 2880 x 1800 <sub>px</sub> | 1440 x 900 <sub>px</sub> | 220 <sub>ppi</sub> | 112 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | macOS Sierra"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-146",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook Pro 2016 13\"",
      "back": "13.4 <sub>inch</sub> | 2560 x 1600 <sub>px</sub> | 1280 x 800 <sub>px</sub> | 227 <sub>ppi</sub> | 113 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | macOS Sierra"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-147",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook Pro 2016 15\"",
      "back": "15.4 <sub>inch</sub> | 2880 x 1800 <sub>px</sub> | 1440 x 900 <sub>px</sub> | 220 <sub>ppi</sub> | 112 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | macOS Sierra"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-148",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook Pro 2017 13\"",
      "back": "13.4 <sub>inch</sub> | 2560 x 1600 <sub>px</sub> | 1280 x 800 <sub>px</sub> | 227 <sub>ppi</sub> | 113 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | macOS Sierra"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-149",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Laptops",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "MacBook Pro 2017 15\"",
      "back": "15.4 <sub>inch</sub> | 2880 x 1800 <sub>px</sub> | 1440 x 900 <sub>px</sub> | 220 <sub>ppi</sub> | 112 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2.0 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | macOS Sierra"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-150",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple Watch SE (40mm) (2020)",
      "back": "1.57 <sub>inch</sub> | 394 x 324 <sub>px</sub> | 197 x 162 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | watchOS 7.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-151",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple Watch SE (44mm) (2020)",
      "back": "1.78 <sub>inch</sub> | 448 x 368 <sub>px</sub> | 224 x 184 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | watchOS 7.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-152",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple Watch Series 3 (38mm)",
      "back": "1.5 <sub>inch</sub> | 340 x 272 <sub>px</sub> | 170 x 136 <sub>px</sub> | 290 <sub>ppi</sub> | 145 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | watchOS 4.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-153",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple Watch Series 3 (42mm)",
      "back": "1.65 <sub>inch</sub> | 390 x 312 <sub>px</sub> | 195 x 156 <sub>px</sub> | 303 <sub>ppi</sub> | 152 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | watchOS 4.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-154",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple Watch Series 4 (40mm)",
      "back": "1.57 <sub>inch</sub> | 394 x 324 <sub>px</sub> | 197 x 162 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | watchOS 5.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-155",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple Watch Series 4 (44mm)",
      "back": "1.78 <sub>inch</sub> | 448 x 368 <sub>px</sub> | 224 x 184 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | watchOS 5.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-156",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple Watch Series 5 (40mm) (2019)",
      "back": "1.57 <sub>inch</sub> | 394 x 324 <sub>px</sub> | 197 x 162 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | watchOS 6.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-157",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple Watch Series 5 (44mm) (2019)",
      "back": "1.78 <sub>inch</sub> | 448 x 368 <sub>px</sub> | 224 x 184 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | watchOS 6.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-158",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple Watch Series 6 (40mm) (2020)",
      "back": "1.57 <sub>inch</sub> | 394 x 324 <sub>px</sub> | 197 x 162 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | watchOS 7.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-159",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Apple Watch Series 6 (44mm) (2020)",
      "back": "1.78 <sub>inch</sub> | 448 x 368 <sub>px</sub> | 224 x 184 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | watchOS 7.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-160",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Asus Zenwatch 2 (2015)",
      "back": "1.63 <sub>inch</sub> | 320 x 320 <sub>px</sub> | 213 x 213 <sub>px</sub> | 278 <sub>ppi</sub> | 185 <sub>ppi</sub> | 1.5 <sub>hdpi</sub> |"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-161",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Asus Zenwatch 3 (2016)",
      "back": "1.39 <sub>inch</sub> | 400 x 400 <sub>px</sub> | 267 x 267 <sub>px</sub> | 287 <sub>ppi</sub> | 191 <sub>ppi</sub> | 1.5 <sub>hdpi</sub> | Android Wear OS 2.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-162",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Asus Zenwatch 3 (2016)",
      "back": "1.39 <sub>inch</sub> | 400 x 400 <sub>px</sub> | 267 x 267 <sub>px</sub> | 287 <sub>ppi</sub> | 191 <sub>ppi</sub> | 1.5 <sub>hdpi</sub> | Android Wear OS 2.1"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-163",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Huawei Watch GT (2018)",
      "back": "1.39 <sub>inch</sub> | 454 x 454 <sub>px</sub> | 227 x 227 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> |"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-164",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Huawei Watch Magic (2018)",
      "back": "1.2 <sub>inch</sub> | 390 x 390 <sub>px</sub> | 195 x 195 <sub>px</sub> | 326 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> |"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-165",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "LG G Watch R (2015)",
      "back": "1.3 <sub>inch</sub> | 320 x 320 <sub>px</sub> | 213 x 213 <sub>px</sub> | 245 <sub>ppi</sub> | 163 <sub>ppi</sub> | 1.5 <sub>hdpi</sub> | Android Wear OS 1.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-166",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "LG Watch Sport (2017)",
      "back": "1.38 <sub>inch</sub> | 480 x 480 <sub>px</sub> | 240 x 240 <sub>px</sub> | 348 <sub>ppi</sub> | 174 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | Android Wear 2.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-167",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "LG Watch Urbane 2nd Edition (2016)",
      "back": "1.38 <sub>inch</sub> | 480 x 480 <sub>px</sub> | 240 x 240 <sub>px</sub> | 348 <sub>ppi</sub> | 174 <sub>ppi</sub> | 2 <sub>xhdpi</sub> | Android Wear 2.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-168",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "LG Watch W7 (2018)",
      "back": "1.2 <sub>inch</sub> | 360 x 360 <sub>px</sub> | 240 x 240 <sub>px</sub> | 300 <sub>ppi</sub> | 200 <sub>ppi</sub> | 1.5 <sub>hdpi</sub> | Android Wear OS 2.0"
    },
    {
      "id": "s2-169",
      "sectionId": "s2",
      "title": "Smart Watch",
      "kind": "qa",
      "front": "Samsung Galaxy Watch (2018)",
      "back": "1.3 <sub>inch</sub> | 360 x 360 <sub>px</sub> | 240 x 240 <sub>px</sub> | 278 <sub>ppi</sub> | 185 <sub>ppi</sub> | 1.5 <sub>hdpi</sub> | Tizen-based <br/>wearable OS 4.0"
    }
  ],
  "source": {
    "repo": "https://github.com/Fechin/reference",
    "path": "source/_posts/resolutions.md",
    "ref": "main",
    "url": "https://github.com/Fechin/reference/tree/main/source/_posts/resolutions.md",
    "lang": "en",
    "mode": "local"
  }
}